Zac Heisey

Web Consultant

Mobile: (408) 444-0546 Email: zheisey@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zacheisey

Portfolio: http://www.zac-heisey.com GitHub: https://github.com/zac-heisey

Introduction

I'm a Baltimore-based web consultant with a passion for helping nonprofits and socially responsible organizations grow online.

I specialize in solving problems and developing strategies across a variety of digital channels in ways that allow organizations to more effectively promote their cause and drive real change.

Relevant Experience

Founder, Lead Consultant - Sage Web Co. - Baltimore, MD Jan. 2016 - Present

- Full-scale web consulting services for nonprofits, including:
 - Digital strategy planning and execution
 - Website design, development, and maintenance
 - Online marketing (SEO, PPC, social media, email, etc.)

Optimization Strategist - Showroom Logic - Remote May 2016 - Feb. 2017

 Management and optimization of ~200 paid search marketing accounts, including budget allocation, ad testing, keyword research, reporting, and analysis

Co-Founder - Tribe Interactive, LLC - Bay Area, CA May 2014 - Dec. 2015

- Oversaw all areas of digital marketing
- Contributed to design and development projects as it pertained to scoping, time & budget management, internal resource management, client communication, testing & QA, and project launch

Education

Nebraska Wesleyan University - Lincoln, NE 2003-2007

- Bachelor of Arts, Communication
- Minor, Public Relations

Skills

HTML/CSS • • • • •

JS/jQuery • • • • •

UI/UX • • • • •

Tools + Tech

WordPress • • • •

Bootstrap • • • • •

Sketch App • • • • •

Git/GitHub • • • •

Projects

Silver Strand Physical Therapy www.silverstrandpt.com

NihonGoFlip

www.zac-heisey.com/nihongoflip

RISE Physical Therapy www.risephysicaltherapy.com

Friday's Child

fridayschildearlylearningcenter.com

Web Development Training

Betamore Academy - Baltimore, MD **Spring 2016**

 Front-End Web Development Certificate (10-week course)